I, Rina Matsuda, will be in charge of the first installment of Sakurazaka Channel's personal project.
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!
It's a beautiful day here in Japan.
What am I going to do today?
I've always wanted to try glamping.
I've always wanted to try glamping, and I'm not sure if I'd be comfortable doing it alone.
So I asked my senior to come today.
Hello, who's there?
Hello!
I'm Yuka.
The wind is just right
This is Ms. Yuka.
It's nice to have you here.
It's been a while.
It's nice to see you.
Thank you very much.
It's okay that you let me come out for the first time like this.
Of course. Thank you.
I'm so glad.
I've always had flyaways on both sides of my hair.
I've been spraying it so it hardens and flies away.
It's a beautiful day today.
Hey, Mr. Nayuka.
It's a super nice day.
I'm a glamping hairdresser.
You really do it with selfies like this, on YouTube.
Yes, I've been doing a little Vlogging myself.
This is only my second vlog, so I'm not used to it.
You can already see it.
Great tent!
Oh, my God!
The lady is out!
The tombola.
Nice job with the tombola!
It's so good!
I like the green!
Amazing!
I didn't know it was so easy to make now.
You're right.
So each of them has their own room?
Yes, there is.
There it is.
How stylish!
You want to come in here?
Wow.
What a board!
A board.
What a stylish board!
It looks like this.
It's like this!
Wow!
Wow.
Wow. - Wow.
It's kind of nice. The colors are kind of warm.
It's great, isn't it?
Shall I show you inside?
Excuse me.
Wow.
It's nice.
It doesn't even hit me in the head.
It feels warm.
Warm.
Yes, it is.
Make your bed.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Just a little practice with the camera marks.
One more time.
Do you think it'll work?
I'd love to, but...
Here we go.
Ready?
Okay.
Wah!Wow.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
heave-ho! - heave-ho!
Wa-ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
It's like the robot of the end of the show.
It really is.
No, it's not.
The bed's not soft either.
It is soft.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Stylish.
The view is great!
It's so nice!
You can see the greenery.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
A very sexy pose!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm so flabbergasted.
It's so thin.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's so thin!
You can see it really well.
It's nice to have a day off like this.
We can go somewhere a little different and relax.
Yes, it's nice, isn't it?
Here we go.
I want to do this.
Wow.
I love this place.
This is great!
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
This way.
Look, it looks like this place.
It's so cute and stylish.
First floor for sure.
Here we go. Nice and stylish.
Let's go.
Oh, he's running!
Mr. Sugai is running!
Hello!
Fashionable!
So stylish...
Looks so delicious!
Choco La Crunch Bananas look delicious too!
Only one!
I don't know about me...
I think I'll have the White Peach and Raisin.
That's totally different!
It's definitely different.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I see.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
The air is so nice.
Isn't that chair cute?
I thought so.
It's so cute.
May I?
It's so tiny.
It's cute.
He's so cute... he looks like he lives in the forest.
I wonder if I can sit on it.
That's nice.
This is where the buttocks go.
It looks so delicious.
This is Yuka's first time.
I'm a little thin.
Bon appétit!
Oh, coffee!
Delicious!
The peach and lychee come first, but it's really good!
Really?
Oh, really?
It's good.
It's good, it's very good.
Very nice, very nice, really relaxing.
This is the view from the festival.
The view from the festival is like this.
You should come, too.
It's so nice.I love it.
I love it. - I love it.
Oh, it's great. It's great. It's a good time.
What do you do on your day off?
On my days off. Recently...
I don't know... in the past... when we were a group...
On my days off, I do all kinds of stuff.
Yes, I understand.
I used to move around like a secretive person.
But recently I've been spending more time alone.
I've been spending more time alone lately.
I go to a riding club and ride horses.
That's great.
The festival is closed these days.
It's not easy, but you're busy with the tours and stuff.
I'm on tour right now.
But you're doing your best to stay busy.
You can tell.
I really like that.
Not thinking about anything else is the best rest I can get.
Oh, wait, Yuka, you're a turtle too?
Ha-ha-ha.
I even titled it "Turtles Outside.
We're perfect for each other.
Excuse me...
Wow, a tree already.
That's a big tree.
Big marshmallows.
Marshmallows.
Let's have a championship to see who can bake the best.
I'm pretty confident.
Me too.
You sure?
One. I'm working on it.
The position is important, too.
It's hard to get it off.
Great!
Okay, let's try Yuka next.
I'll go next
This one looks easy to stick
Oh, that's good
Wow, that's good
I always connect them together, but with this size...
That's true.
Let's go grill.
I love the sound of bonfires.
There was a radio that only had the sound of a bonfire, right?
I used to listen to them with an app.
I listened to it a lot.
Do you sleep well?
Yes, but when I go to bed, I notice that the sound bothers me.
I find it hard to sleep.
I really like the sound.
When did you realize that marshmallows are delicious?
Well, when was it?
But I don't know. I was in elementary school.
Really?
Me too. Bird-watching?
Bird-watching?
When I was in elementary school, we had this event.
Afterwards, we would eat roasted marshmallows together.
That's where I first learned about them.
I've been buying marshmallows ever since.
I'd buy marshmallows, stick them in disposable chopsticks, and burn them over a flame.
I know, I know.
Oh, here it is.
You like Yuka, don't you?
Wait, it's like an Erengi, it's like an Erengi
Wait, black, black...
It's a little flammable.
Great, let's eat!
Sounds good.
Delicious!
Delicious, sweet, and juicy inside.
It doesn't look like it, but I'm eating mushrooms.
The color and shape are amazing!
Good color. It's good. It's my favorite color for the festival, the fox color.
Good. - Good.
It's cute.
How's it look?How is it?
It's soft and fluffy. It's perfect.
It's perfect.
Weak. Wow.
Echoes.
I'll take it like that... it's so small... it's good!
Oh!
Let's have lunch next!
Yay!
I just had a snack.
I'm the type of person who eats snacks first.
Wow!
I can't believe I did that.
Stylish!
I wonder where we are.
Wow, where is our camp?
Where is our camp?
I think it's at the very back.
Look at this!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow.
Oh, wow!
So stylish!
I don't know what it is about this wood.
I love the plates.
Wow!
Looks delicious!
There's a shrimp, too!
Beautiful!
I don't know where to start. There's so many things to do.
I'm sure we'll have plenty to start with.
I want to bake some onions.
I'll put it down.
I'll put it down. - These...
Great, I'll put it down.
Please, put it here.
Carrots.
That carrot is confusing, isn't it?
It's not like they're facing each other or anything.
I don't know if it's okay.
But I can eat them.
Really?
Horses eat them straight up.
With a horse?
Then what is it?
Vegetables for now.
I'll grill them.
Thank you.
It sounds so good, I think it's going to burn soon.
Oh, good.
Which one do you want to grill, ma'am?
I want to grill some corn.
Let's cook some corn.
Can I grill it as it is?
Let's go, let's go!
It's like in a cartoon.
Here you go.
So cute!
It's a vertical type.
Do you cook any meat?
Yes, that's right.
Wow, it's thick.
Here we go.
Wow!
Sounds good.
Yummy!
And now we're grilling!
Oh, shrimp!
Soy milk.
Is this okay?
I just did it with my bare hands.
Beautiful. Looks delicious.
Is it ready?
Looks good.
I like it. I like it.
I like the angle of view.
You like it?
It's not a very pretty plate.
A little burnt carrot.Slightly charred carrot
Bon appétit!
By all means, Yuka, start with the one you're interested in.
Thank you. Bon appétit.
Then, the meat Matsuri cut for us.
Oh, it's so thick!
May I? Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Thick.
I cut it a little bigger.
It's not exactly bite-sized.
I didn't know you could eat so much of it!
So tender!
So juicy!
I'm so glad!
Bon appétit!
Meat
The oil is delicious.
Mmm.
Anyone get the vibe? Everyone's new here.
But...
Surprisingly, everyone is talking a lot with the 3rd term students.
The 2nd-term students are really very active in talking to the 3rd-term students.
The third-term students talk to me a lot, too.
Really?
That's great. The atmosphere seems to have changed a little bit.
Many of them are very active, and they talk to me.
They talk to me, so that makes me really happy.
Take a shortcut in the summer.
It's nice, isn't it?
And Sakurazuki was great, too.
I liked the music video for "Happening Cool" so much I watched it several times.
Oh, I see, I'm so glad!
It's the first time for everyone to tie two knots in a music video, right?
It was like everyone was tying two knots in the music video.
No, I don't think so.
But I think it's because it's easier to hold the hair when you're swinging.
And the costumes were cute and waitress-like.
I think there were a lot of them.
The characters in the music video were really cute.
The one that everyone is looking at while riding like this.
I wish they would release some T-shirts or something like that.
I know, I'm a fan too.
I wanted to get some stickers or something with that character on it.
Yes, of course.
I'm also interested in the corn, and I want to see the shrimp.
Okay, I'll start with the ones I like.
Hey, let's just do it with our hands already.
That's nice. Corn.
Oh, I wonder what it looks like.
Oh, the skin is really nice, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I've never eaten this type of corn like this before.
Oh, wow.
Is there? Is it inside?
Where is it?
Oh, is it gonna end up like this?
Is that it?
Which one do you like better?
Oh, the young corn.
Not corn?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, my gosh.
That's great.
Young corn.
Young corn. Wow.
Take a bite.
Oh, I can do it! I can do it!
I can do it!
I can eat that much!
Is it good?
Yes!
I ate it.
Like an elbow.
I can eat it!
You can eat it!
It's a bit of a waste.
You can go there.
I've never eaten here before.
Wow!
Looks delicious!Looks delicious!
But it's turning red. It's burnt.
It looks burnt, doesn't it?
Thanks for the shrimp.
I'll take life.
Mr. Yuka...
Now that you've graduated.
You're looking at the group from the outside.
What do you think? Our
Our activities
What's it like?
From a distance.
Seeing how hard you guys are working?
That's exactly what the single is about.
Sakurazuki, the first single without me, and from an objective point of view
I was happy to see how hard everyone was working.
I was so happy.
I was happy to see everyone working so hard.
now that I'm away from them, I think that they're all
They are all cute idols.
I think they're so precious.
I think they're precious.
When I go to live shows...
Idols are so special
Only now
I can only support them now.
It's amazing.
I still say you should push for your idols when you can.
LOL!
I lost my neck.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Talk to me.
Maybe I didn't ask at the right time.
Looks good.
Just the way I like it.
Bon appétit.
You go first.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
Bon appétit.
It's gone.
Mmm!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I'm devouring it.
Oh, man.
That's not very idol friendly.
I ate the whole thing.
I could eat around here, too.
Yes, I could.
It tastes like young corn.
I didn't know they were this good.
Young corn?
You don't have to pull out a lot of it.
No need to pull it out.
But it's a little tasty, like the taste of freshness.
It's like a reed.
Oh, my gosh!
I ate the tail.
I really like the series of eating everything at the festival!
I can see the sparkling sea so much!
The ocean!
I'm so happy!
Glamping viewing & sea viewing
This is a great place to enjoy glamping and see the ocean!
This is a great spot!
It's a great spot for glamping!
It's a nice spot.
It's so beautiful.
It's the ocean.
I can see the Sky Tree over there.
Can you see the Sky Tree?
You can see the Sky Tree?
Can you see it?
I can see it.
Fuji or something.
I can't see it.
This is my favorite one.
Thank you for such an important YouTube.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since I've been a member of this group, and I feel like a little bit of a member again.I felt a little bit like a member again after all these years.
I was already acting like a normal member of the same group.
I couldn't do the rest.
I wanted to do the festival that was so much fun.
That's right.
I'm glad I got to have fun with you.
I'm glad I got to play it so well.
Thank you very much.
I'll be rooting for you in relation to this.
I'll do my best.
I want to do my best, and I'm looking forward to working with you buddies.
I'll be asking for your help from now on
Thank you very much for the fun, good luck, and the keys.